(Sheldon:)I assume
you were opening with a joke.
(Sheldon:)It certainly buoyed up
this employee's esprit de corps.
(Leonard:)It's not a joke.
It's the real design.
(Sheldon:)In that case, may I offer
27 little tweaks
(Sheldon:)to make it
slightly less embarrassing?
(Leonard:)Sheldon, I think
this will work.
(Leonard:)Let's just try it my way.
Oh, I'm-I'm sorry.
(Sheldon:)I assumed that you wanted
(Sheldon:)candid truth-telling
from your employees,
(Sheldon:)but I realize now,
you want the mindless nattering
(Sheldon:)of complacent
yes-men.
(Leonard:)Are you done?
(Sheldon:)If you say so, boss.
(Howard:)So right now,
this button-press event
(Howard:)is just triggering
a dummy procedure call...
(Sheldon:)How about this
for the app name?
(Sheldon:)The Surprisingly
Helpful Equation-Linked
(Leonard:)Differential
Optimized Numerator.
So it spells "Sheldon."
(Sheldon:)Does it?
(Sheldon:)A happy accident.
(Leonard:)We're not doing
names now. Howard?
(Howard:)Like I was saying, right now
it's just a dummy procedure,
(Howard:)but eventually,
it will drop us into...